That’s what we’re searching for—
Questo è quello che stiamo cercando,
the imperfect is searching for the Perfect.
l'imperfetto sta cercando il Perfetto.
[What do We Live For]
[Per Cosa Stiamo Vivendo?]
We’re searching for the Ideal.
Stiamo cercando l'ideale.
for the Absolute.
Stiamo cercando l'Assoluto.
That is what life is.
Questo è la vita.
existence is actually.
Questo è ciò che è l'esistenza in realtà.
It’s not a religion, a religious thing, a religious idea.
Non è una religione, una cosa religiosa, un'idea religiosa.
It’s Reality.
È la Realtà.
As once Guru Mahārāj said,
Come disse una volta Guru Mahārāj:
“Kṛṣṇa consciousness is Reality,
«La coscienza di Kṛṣṇa è la Realtà
and it’s in your interest
ed è nel tuo interesse
to become acquainted with this Reality.”
prendere confidenza con questa Realtà».
It’s not Hinduism or an Indian religion,
Non è induismo o una religione indiana
or something a particular group of people believe.
o qualcosa a cui crede un particolare gruppo di persone.
It’s Reality.
«È la Realtà».
We have to start thinking of it that way.
Dobbiamo cominciare a pensarla in questa maniera.
Therefore he used that expression:
Perciò ha usato l'espressione
“Reality the Beautiful.”
"La Bella Realtà".
“Search for Śrī Kṛṣṇa, Reality the Beautiful.”
"La ricerca di Śrī Kṛṣṇa, la Bella Realtà".
“The Ultimate Reality is beautiful.”
"La Realtà Suprema è bella".